<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SEO-CHECKLIST</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">More Infos</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>
    <string name="menu_tools">Tools</string>
    <string name="menu_share">Share</string>
    <string name="menu_send">Visit our WebSite</string>
    <string name="menu_dev">Developed by</string>
    <string name="title_activity_more">MoreActivity</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        More Info : This extension is a tool designed to help you focus on the top youtube and video SEO ranking factors pulled from several reputable industry reports and top SEO experts.
    For a more in depth explanation, see the Step By Step YouTube SEO Checklist 2019 Version blog post which has info for each step and one paragraph description of each point.
    I refer to the “blog post” within the checklist several times where i recommend free tools or a tutorial that helps or explains some steps of this checklist.
    These are SEO and traffic strategies designed to help you drive more traffic through your videos.\n
    You can check your optimization score and see it improve with each task that you complete from the automated scorer at the bottom of the extension
    \n
    \n
    Recommended YouTube SEO Software : You Can Automate Your YouTube Video, Channel and Playlist Optimization Using The Following Tools Which All Have Built In Strategies Made Checkbox Simple!
    \n
    Tubekit Alpha (Video and Channel Optimization Software)\n
    Video Synd Alpha (Video Distribution Software)\n
    Vid Attack Alpha (Increase User Behaviour Signals: CTR From SERPS  and Retention)\n
    Vid Curate Alpha (Powerful YouTube Playlist Ranking and Social Video Curation Tools)\n
    Multi-Feed RSS Plugin (Create Playlists From Channel, Videos, Playlists With RSS Syndication)\n
    \n
    \n
    \n
Free Tools, Tutorials and Resources : You Can Automate Your YouTube Video, Channel and Playlist Optimization Using The Following Tools Which All Have Built In Strategies Made Checkbox Simple!
\n
   Free Tools\n
    Make YouTube Thumbnails With This Free Tool\n
    Ubersuggest Free Keyword Tool\n
    Get a Free One Site License For WordPress RSS Xtreme\n

        Recommended Tutorials, Blog Posts and Cheat Sheets\n
        Viral Content: 21 Data-Driven Techniques That Work Fast\n
        51 Headline Formulas For Higher Conversions\n
        Content Upgrade Ideas To Grow Your Email List\n
        Coschedule Headline Analyzer\n
        401 Headline POWER WORDS\n
        Top Headline Phrases Analyzed\n
        Sumo Swipe File\n
        Headlines: Analysis of 10 Million Articles Shared on LinkedIn\n
        \n
            Create Checklists with these tools\n
            Tools to easily create checklists: Forget and Checklist\n
            </string>
</resources>
